Guide to the Andrew F. Smith Collection of Cookery Ephemera MSS.295
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Cookery Ephemera, 1798-2009
  - University of Texas--Nuts, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Rich, Jessie P. "Nuts And Their Uses As Food," Bulletin of the University of Texas, No. 366, Extension Series No. 63. Austin, TX: Department Of Extension, Division Of Home Welfare, University of Texas, October 20, 1915.
  - The U.S. Playing Card Company, 1921 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    U.S. Playing Card Company. How to Entertain with Cards: Private Parties, Public Parties, Social Clubs. Cincinnati, OH: U.S. Playing Card Company, 1921.
  - Vermont Department of Agriculture--McIndoes Grange, No. 306, circa 1900 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Vermont Guild Of Old Time Crafts & Industries--Corn, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Vermont Maple Sugar Exchange, circa 1890 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Vermont Maple Sugar Exchange. Maple Sugar Cook Book. Brattleboro: Vermont Maple Sugar Exchange, circa 1890.
  - Valentine, Mann S., 1886 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - V. La Rosa & Sons, Inc., 1947 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    Rosa & Sons. La Rosa 51 Pastina Recipes. Brooklyn: V. La Rosa & Sons, Inc., 1947.
  - Walker & Pratt Manufacturing Company, 1893 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Walker & Pratt Mfg. Co. Lincoln, Mary J. Twelve New Recipes. Boston, MA: Walker & Pratt Mfg. Co, 1893.
  - Walker Austex Chili Company, 1930s (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Walker's Austex Chili. International Recipes with the Magic of Seasoning. Mexene Chili Powder Seasoning. Austin, TX: Walker's Austex Chili, 1930s.
  - Walter Baker & Company, Ltd., circa 1880, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    Walter Baker and Company. Choice Recipes. Dorchester, MA: Walter Baker & Co., Ltd., 1916.
    Walter Baker and Company. Manufacturing of Chocolate Coca & Broma Prescriptions. Dorchester, MA: Walter Baker and Co., undated.
    Walter Baker and Company. Chocolate Receipts. Dorchester, MA: Walter Baker & Co., circa 1880.
  - Walter M. Lowney Company, 1904 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    Walter M. Lowney. Lowney's New Receipt-Book. Boston, MA: The Walter M. Lowney Co., 1904.
  - The Wander Company--Ovaltine, 1930s (Box 40, Folder 24)
    The Wander Company. Ovaltine: The Swiss Food Development (Now Made in America). Villa Park, IL: The Wander Company, circa 1930.
  - Warrenton Clam Company, 1910-1920s (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Warrenton Clam Co. Warrenton Clams Sixteen Recipes Aristocrat-of the Dinner Table. Portland, OR: Warrenton Clam Co., undated.
  - Washburn Crosby Company, 1894, 1910-1920s (Box 40, Folder 26-28)
    Washburn-Crosby Co. "Gold Medal Flour." (ephemera– single sheet) Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
    Washburn-Crosby Co. Gold Medal Flour Cook Book. Minneapolis, MN: Washburn-Crosby Co., 1917.
  - Washburn-Wilson Seed Company, 1910-1920s (Box 40, Folder 29)
    Washburn-Wilson Seed Co. Washburn's Fancy Peas. Moscow, Idaho: Washburn-Wilson Seed Co., undated.
  - Washington Service Bureau, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    Washington Service Bureau. Trappe, Ruth. Salads and Sandwiches. Washington, DC: Washington Service Bureau, 1937.
  - Water Front Grocery Company, Limited, 1885 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    Water Front Grocery Co. Weekly Price Current. Brooklyn, NY: Water Front Grocery Co., February 9, 1885.
  - Waterhouse, John, 1867 (Box Shared Fales 003, Folder 6)
  - W. Atlee Burpee & Company, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    Burpee. Scott, Anna B. Best Ways to Cook Fresh Vegetables. Philadelphia, PA: W. Atlee Burpee & Co., 1915.
  - Waukesha Pure Food Company--Jiffy-Jell, circa 1916 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Waybest Poultry, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Webber, Carolyn Putnam, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    Webber, Carolyn Putnam. Dozens of Good Things. Bedford, MA: The Bedford Print Shop, 1915.
  - Weber-Stephen Products Company, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - W. E. Drislane Company, 1914 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    W. E. Drislane Company. Drislane Quarterly [Formerly The American Table]. Albany, NY: publisher unknown, 1914.
  - Wehman Brothers, 1891-1909 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Welch Grape Fruit Juice Company, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Welch Grape Juice Company. Welch's Mother - Daughter Cook Book. Westfield, NY: Welch Grape Juice Company, 1946.
  - Wesson Oil, 1913-1932 (Box 41, Folder 6-7)
    Southern Cotton Oil Co. Rorer, Sarah T. Recipes. New York, NY: Southern Cotton Oil Co., 1913.
    Wesson Oil. Salad Styles. New York, NY: A. E. Dittrich [sic] Ltd., Printing, undated.
    Wesson Oil. Murray, Mary B. "Let's Enjoy Eating.". New Orleans, LA: The Wesson Oil and Snowdrift People, 1932.
    Wesson. Adventures of the Veg-eat-eers with 200 New, Tasty Vegetable Recipes Tested by the Good Housekeeping Institute. Place of publication unknown: publisher unknown, undated.
  - West Bend Aluminum Company, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    West Bend Aluminum. American Waterless Cooker Recipe Book Roasting-Cooking-Preserving. West Bend, WI: West Bend Aluminum Co., 1927.
  - W. F. Robinson & Company, 1885 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - W. G. Thomas, 1879 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Whipple, Wayne, 1903 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Whipple, Wayne. The Story of the White House And its Home Life. Boston, MA: Dwinell-Wright Company, 1903.
  - White & Howland, 1872 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    White & Howland. The Household Companion and Family Receipt Book. New York, NY: White and Howland, 1872.
  - White Castle System, Inc., 1940 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    White Castle System, Inc. A National Institution. 39th Printing. Columbus, OH: White Castle System, Inc. August 1940.
  - The White Mountain Freezer Company, 1905 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    White Mountain Freezer. Lincoln, Mary J., ed. Frozen Dainties. Nashua, NH: White Mountain Freezer Co., 1905.
  - White-Stokes Company, Inc., 1910-1920 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    White-Stokes Co. White-Stokes Mallo Icing and Topping for Cakes. Chicago, IL: White-Stokes Co., undated.
  - Whitman's Chocolates & Confections, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Wiland & Company, 1850-1880s (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Wiland & Co. "Saratoga Chipper." Broadside for Peeler, Corer and Slicer. Philadelphia, PA: Wiland & Co., undated.
  - The William G. Bell Company, 1878-1922 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    Bell Co. Recipes by Famous New England Chefs. Boston, MA: William G. Bell Co., undated.
  - William L. Clements Library--Longone Center for American Culinary Research, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Williams, John & Cindy, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Wilson & Company, Ham, 1850-1880s (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Winslow, William B., 1884 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - W. Kelly Milling Company, 1880-1910 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    Kelly Mills. Kelly's Famous Flour. Hutchinson, KS: Kelly Mills, undated.
  - The Woman's Club of Albuquerque, NM, 1904-1905 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    The Woman's Club of Albuquerque, NM. Tested Recipes For Cuisine. Albuquerque, NM: Commercial Printing Company. 1904-1905.
  - Woman's Day Kitchen #227: Cakes & Cookies, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Woman's Home Companion, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    Woman's Home Companion. Gypsy Meals: Outdoor Cookery & Picnic Eats. New York, NY: Woman's Home Companion, 1928.
  - The Woman's Society of The Congregational Church of Holden, MA, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - The Women of the Washington Heights Baptist Church, 1900-1920s (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Womens' Auxiliary of Westminster Presbyterian Church, 1900-1920s (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Women's Missionary Society--The Methodist Church, Prescott, AZ, 1930-1940s (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Women's Missionary Society of United Presbyterian Church, Conneaut Lake, PA, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Wood, Pollard & Company, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    Wood, Pollard & Company. The Esculent: For Advancement Of The Best Eating, Retail Price List. Boston, MA: Wood Pollard & Company, Importers and Grocers, January 1906.
  - Woods, Sherwood & Company, 1868 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Woods, Sherwood & Co. The Household Companion for 1868. Lowell, MA: Woods, Sherwood & Co. 1868.
  - The Woolverton Printing & Publishing Company, 1900-1920s (Box 42, Folder 2)
    The Woolverton Printing & Publishing Company. The Candy Book. Osage, IA: The Woolverton Printing & Publishing Company, undated.
  - World's Columbian Fair, Chicago, 1893 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - W. P. Plumer, 1886 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Plumer. New England Home Reference. Newburyport, MA: W. I. Goods and Groceries, 1886.
  - Wright's Smoke Company, 1970s (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - W. S. Quinby Company--Teas, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - W. T. Soule & Company--Wheat, 1879 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - W. Zinsser & Company--Salicylic Acid, 1897-1910 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    W. Zinsser & Co. The United States Salicylic Acid Works. New York, NY: W. Zinsser & Co., undated.
  - Young, Anne M., 1903 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Peoples Gas, Light & Coke Co. Young, Anne M., arr. Bills of Fare. Chicago, IL: Rogers & Wells, 1903.
  - Young Women's Christian Temperance Union (Y.W.C.T.U.), 1898 (Box 42, Folder 10)